impressionsvanity.com 2016-09-12

# Impressions Vanity Co. | Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

* * *

##### WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

We collect information from you when you visit our site, register on our site, place an order, or subscribe to our newsletter. When ordering or registering on our site, when applicable, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may also visit our site anonymously.

##### HOW IS YOUR INFORMATION USED?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one, or more, of the following ways:  
**Personally Identifiable Information:**  We collect information that can be used to identify you as an individual (“Personally Identifiable Information”) only when you provide such information directly to us in connection with the Service.

  * We may use your information to process transactions; your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * We may use the Personally Identifiable Information we collect or receive to communicate directly with you. We may also send you emails containing newsletters, promotions, and special offers. If you do not want to receive such email messages, we will give you the option to opt out or change your preferences. We also use your Personally Identifiable Information to send you Service-related emails or other emails that we believe may interest you (e.g., account verification, purchase and billing confirmations and reminders, changes/updates to features of the Service, technical and security notices). You may not opt out of Service-related emails. As discussed below, we may also combine your Personally Identifiable Information with third-party analytics information to build a broader profile of our individual Users.

 **Non-Personally Identifiable Information:**  We also collect and use information about your interactions with the Service in a manner and format that does not identify you as an individual (“Non-Personally Identifiable Information”). We may collect, use, and disclose the following types of Non-Personally Identifiable Information:

  * For Google Adwords marketing purposes: **  THIS WEBSITE USES GOOGLE ADWORDS AND ANALYTICS ADVERTISING FEATURES.** This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Impressions Vanity website. Any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy. You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences page](https://impressionscdn-impressionsvanit.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/onweb), and if you want to you can [opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings](https://impressionscdn-impressionsvanit.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/11/onweb) or [permanently using a browser plugin](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/intl/en/plugin/).
  * Analytics information. We use third-party analytics tools to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Service. These tools collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, including the web pages you visit, your browser add-ons, your browser’s width and height, and other information that assists us in improving the Service. We may collect and use this analytics information together with your Personally Identifiable Information to build a broader profile of our individual Users so that we can serve you better, to improve the Service and for internal business purposes. We may disclose this combined information to our third-party business partners in aggregated, anonymized form as described below in the section entitled “Sharing of Your Information — Non-Personally Identifiable Information.”
  * Google Analytics: We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of the Service, including the Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting feature. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit the Service, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to visiting the Service. We use the information we get from Google Analytics to maintain and improve the Service, and we may share anonymous statistical information from our use of Google Analytics with our business partners for such purposes. Google Analytics collects the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit the Service, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to the Service is restricted by the[Google Analytics Terms of Service](http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html), and the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to the Service by disabling cookies on your browser. In addition, if you want to prevent your data from being provided to Google Analytics, you can [learn how to opt out using a Google plug-in](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)
  * Cookies information: When you visit the Service, we may send one or more cookies — a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters — to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets Impressions Vanity help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie may also convey information to us about how you use the Service (e.g., the pages you view, the links you click, and other actions you take on the Service), and allow us or our business partners to track your usage of the Service over time. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.
  * Log file information: Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page. When you use our Service, our servers (whether operated by us or a third-party provider) automatically record certain log file information. These server logs may include anonymous information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the Service, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information.
  * Clear gifs/web beacons information: When you use the Service, we may employ clear gifs (also known as web beacons), which are used to anonymously track the online usage patterns of our Users. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our Users to track which emails are opened and which links are clicked by recipients. This information allows for more accurate reporting and improvement of the Service.
  * Device identifiers: When you access the Service by or through a mobile device (including but not limited to smartphones or tablets), we may access, collect, monitor, and/or remotely store one or more “device identifiers,” such as a unique device identifier (“UDID”). Device identifiers are small data files or similar data structures stored on or associated with your mobile device, which uniquely identify your mobile device. A device identifier may be data stored in connection with the device hardware, data stored in connection with the device’s operating system or other software, or data sent to the device byImpressions Vanity. A device identifier may convey information to us about how you browse and use the Service. A device identifier may remain persistently on your device to help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the Service. Some features of the Service may not function properly if use or availability of device identifiers is impaired or disabled.
  * Location data: When you access the Service by or through a mobile device, we may access, collect, monitor, and/or remotely store “location data,” which may include GPS coordinates (e.g. latitude and/or longitude) or similar information regarding the location of your mobile device. Location data may convey to us information about how you browse and use the Service. Some features of the Service, particularly location-based services, may not function properly if use or availability of location data is impaired or disabled.
  * Use of Non-Personally Identifiable Information we collect: We use or may use cookies, log file, device identifiers, location data and clear gifs information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) to provide and monitor the effectiveness of our Service; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns; (e) diagnose or fix technology problems; (f) help you efficiently access your information after you sign in; (g) provide advertising to your browser or device.

##### HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.

Impressions Vanity Co. cares about the security of your information and uses commercially reasonable safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of all information collected through the Service. However, Impressions Vanity Co. cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Impressions Vanity Co. or guarantee that information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed. Your privacy settings may also be affected by changes to the functionality of third party integrations, such as social networks. Impressions Vanity Co. is not responsible for the functionality or security measures of any third party.

Compromise of information: In the event that any information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, Impressions Vanity Co. will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation and, where appropriate, notify those individuals whose information may have been compromised and take other steps, in accordance with any applicable laws and regulations.

#####  DO WE USE COOKIES?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.

##### DO WE DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

##### OTHER WEBSITES AND SERVICES; THIRD PARTY LINKS:

Occasionally at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website.We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites or services linked to or from the Service, including the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Service to another website, our Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party websites or services. Your browsing and interaction on any third-party website or service, including those that have a link on our website, are subject to that third party’s own rules and policies. In addition, you agree that we are not responsible for and do not control any third parties that you authorize to access your User Content. If you are using a third-party website or service (like Facebook) and you allow such a third party access to your User Content, you do so at your own risk. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from sources other than through the Service.

##### CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE:

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information, at any time, by logging into their control panel and going to the “Edit Profile” page.

##### CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE:

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act). We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

##### ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY ONLY:

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

##### CONTACTING US

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

Impressions Vanity Co.  
855-373-9983  
1060 N. Batavia St., Unit K  
Orange, CA 92867  

##### CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

Impressions Vanity Co. may, in its sole discretion, modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time, so you should review this page periodically. When we change the policy in a material manner, we will update the “last modified” date at the bottom of this page.

This privacy policy was last modified on 3/7/16 and was first made effective on 11/04/14.
